Minsuk Chang

Ph.D. Student

Georgia Institute of Technology · School of Interactive Computing

■ jangsus1@snu.ac.kr | ★ minsukchang.info

About	
My primary research interests lie in Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) and Informat interested in the graphical perception of humans and the ways in which individuals i visualizations and charts. I primarily target my research towards visualization and HC ACM CHI.	nterpret and understand various
Education	
Georgia Institute of Technology PH.D. STUDENT • School of Interactive Computing • Advisor: Dr. Cindy Xiong Bearfield	Atlanta, GA 2024.08 -
Seoul National University BACHELOR OF SCIENCE • Major: Computer Science and Engineering • GPA: 3.61/4.3 (In-Major 3.75)	Seoul, Korec 2018.03 - 2024.02
Publications	
PUBLISHED	
Assessing Graphical Perception of Image Embedding Models using Channel Effective Seokhyeon Park, and Jinwook Seo. 2023 IEEE Visualization and Visual Analyt	
CLeVer: Continual Learning Visualizer for Detecting Task Transition Failure. Minsu	ık Chang et al. IEEE PacificVis '24
Tensor Space Model-based Textual Data Augmentation for Text Classification. Min '23	nsuk Chang , Han-Joon Kim. IEEE BigData
PRE-PRINTS	
Extracting Human Attention through Crowdsourced Patch Labeling. Minsuk Cha 2024	ng et al. arXiv preprint arXiv:2403.15013
Research Experience	
Seoul National University - Human-Computer Interaction Lab Advisor: Prof. Jinwook Seo	July. 2023 - July. 202 ²
University of Seoul - Data Mining Lab	0
Advisor: Prof. Han-joon Kim	Sept. 2022 - Feb. 2024

Industrial Experience _____

ADVISOR: PROF. YOUNGKI LEE

Seoul National University - Human-Centered System Lab

April. 2022 - June. 2022

Naver Appolo Dev. Pangyo, Korea

UNDERGRADUATE INTERNSHIP

Jan. 2023 - Feb. 2023

 Interned at Naver Corporation and researched how to extract trending topics from user-generated content. Learned non-ML techniques for analyzing time-series data. Used different clustering methods and seasonal algorithms to identify topics linked to specific dates.

PrompTechnology Seoul, Korea

WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERNSHIP

July. 2022 - Aug. 2022

• Worked on modules for the Public Data Portal run by the Ministry of Public Administration and Security. Created an improved cache system to handle high traffic, up to 100 API calls per second. Gained experience with MSA architecture and learned multiple languages and protocols like golang, typescript, and grpc.

Airforce, Republic of Korea

Korea

SYSTEM MANAGEMENT ASSISTANT

Sept. 2020 - March. 2022

• Served in the military as a system management assistant in the Korea Air Force. Managed various database servers and tactical systems. Learned about potential system failures and how to address them effectively.

PrompTechnology Seoul, Korea

WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERNSHIP

July. 2020 - Aug. 2020

• Interned at PrompTechnology and served as a project manager. Developed a survey platform web service using Node.js and Express.js. Gained practical skills in building commercial services. Collaborated with the Graduate School of Public Health at Seoul National University to develop a mental care application for COVID-19 self-quarantine.

Competitions & Projects _____

Reinforcement Learning for Game Yahtzee

Personal Project 2021 - 2022

• Inspired by Reinforcement Learning, developed a Deep Q Network-based AI which plays the board game Yahtzee. Adjusted the model and hyper-parameters to surpass human average scores of 200. Codes and reports are available on GitHub.

AI Hackathon Competition

THE 3RD AI X BOOKATHON BY SKKU&MINDSLAB

Nov. 2021

• Trained a GPT-2 model to write essays on the theme "Together." Used data collected from websites and preprocessed it. Project details and results are available on GitHub.

CloudNews

2021 MILITARY OPEN DATA COMPETITION BY ROKAF

May 2021 - July 2022

• <u>CloudNews</u> is a web service designed to gather all military news and articles scattered around. Used OCR to extract newspaper's text data and visualized its keywords as a cloud map. Participated during military service (2020.06 - 2022.04)

Awards, Fellowships, & Grants ______

Fall, 2023	Academic Achievement Scholarship (Fully Funded), Jeongheon Foundation	\$ 2,300
Spring, 2023	Academic Achievement Scholarship (Fully Funded), Jeongheon Foundation	\$ 2,300

Technical Skills _____

PL Python, C, Cuda, Javascript, Advanced

Web NodeJS, Django, ReactJS, D3, Advanced

English Proficiency _____

TOEFL

Overall Score: 112 (R:30, L:28, S:28, W:26)

July, 8, 2023

Minsuk Chang CV 2